Okay, so we're going to start talking
about something called loops or it's
also called repetition. Repetition
allows you to repeat your code without
having to repeat the actual code itself.
Um, but before we get into that, we
first need to talk about counting. So
bear with me here, but if I asked you to
start at one, count to 10, and go up by
one, you could probably do that. In
fact, I'm going to look a little
ridiculous doing this to the camera, but
one, two, three, four, five, six, seven,
eight, nine, 10. Um, I bet if I
challenged you, you probably could start
at zero, count up by two, and go to 20.
In fact, 0 2 4 6 8 10 12 14 16 18 20.
Um, if I told you to start at 10 and
count backwards to zero and go by one,
you could probably do it. 10 98765 43 22
1. Um, hopefully that wasn't too
difficult for any of you. Um, but if you
noticed when I gave the instructions for
counting, I first gave you where I
wanted you to start, then I gave you
where I wanted you to go, and then I
gave you how much to change by. And if
you can do that, then you can do four
loops, which is what we're going to talk
about